# AASHISH MALLICK

- +977-9844329569
- mallickaashish86@gmail.co m
- New Baneshwor, Kathmandu, Nepal
- https://github.com/amallick 86

## **SKILLS**

- Golang
- Flutter
- AWS
- GCP
- MYSQL
- SQL
- Postgresql
- Firebase
- Docker
- Kubernetes
- CI/CD
- Linux
- WebSocket
- React

# **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Nepali

## **HOBBIES**

- Cooking
- Playing video games

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Organized Golang Developer offering 1 year of Organizational experience . Expert troubleshooter with superior diagnosis and resolution skills. Evaluates performance and implements corrective actions to mitigate challenges and reduce risk. Quickly understands requirements for new systems and creates robust code. Familiar with testing, debugging, and correcting problems found in existing software systems.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER (GOLANG DEVELOPER)

## Seva Development, Lalitpur, Nepal

March 2022- July 2022 (had to take a break for final semester examination)

- Successfully configured and managed GCP for the development and release environment.
- Worked on Golang for the API development.
- Contributed to code reviews, debugging, and optimization.
- Worked within Agile frameworks to consistently meet project timelines and deliverable objectives.
- Successfully created a 'cron job' for the task scheduling.
- Used goroutine and channel to achieve concurrency.

#### GOLANG DEVELOPER

Nandi Technology, Jawalakhel, Lalitpur, Nepal July 2021- March 2022

- Led team of 4 junior software developer undertaking the software development life cycle for inside projects
- Successfully generated backend programming using Golang and Mysql on microservices architecture
- Successfully implemented CI/CD for development, staging and production environment using github workflow
- Sucessfully containerized the application using Docker and we used kubernetes for the automating deployment and scaling.
- Sucessfully implemented Chat system and Quiz game using WebSocket.

### **EDUCATION**

#### BACHELOR OF COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Cosmos College Of Management and Technology, Tutepani, ChapagaunDobato, Lalitpur, Nepal 2018 - Waiting for final semester result

#### HSEB(+2)

NASA International College, Tinkune, Kathmandu, Nepal 2014 - 2017

#### SLC

New English Higher Secondary School, Janakpur, Nepal 2002 - 2014